One.
I work with who tries if we are here vibing.
We vibing.
Even when it's raining down.
Can't stop now.
Can't stop so shut your mouth.
Shut your mouth.
And if you don't know then now you know it's fake.
Know it's fake, yeah.
Right now I'm in a state of mind.
I wanna be in that cold inside.
And I know tears have to cry.
So I'm making it up.
Oh yeah.
Oh I just want you to come with me.
We are the love of mentality.
And I know tears have to cry.
So I'm making it up.
I'm making it up.
Loving, not living so we turning up.
We turning up.
When I'm pulling out the colors in you.
I see them doing boy I like them.
I like them.
We ain't too blind about taking all this hate.
We are here vibing.
We vibing.
Baby yeah yeah.
Even when it's raining down.
Can't not feel shut your mouth.
You know it's fake.
And if you don't know then now you know it's fake.
Know it's fake, yeah.
Right now I'm in a state of mind.
I wanna be in that cold inside.
And I know tears have to cry.
So I'm making it up.
Oh yeah.
I know I'm not gonna come with me.
We all know I'm not gonna tell you.
And I know tears have to cry.
So I'm making it up.
Yeah yeah yeah.
I'm making it up.
Even when it's raining down.
Oh yeah.
I got those tears but you're mine.
We all know I'm not gonna tell you.
And I know tears have to cry.
So I'm making it up.
I'm making it up.
Love and I'm living so we turn it up.
Yeah, we turn it up.